Shubham Rishi

Abbotsford, BC V2S 5N8 shubhamangras@hotmail.com +1 236 458 1757

I love learning, as it is a lifelong process. Currently, I am a full-time student who is pursuing his bachelor's program in the field of computer science from UFV.I have a lot of experience related to Computers(Software and Hardware). I would love to gain valuable experience which will be beneficial for me in the future.

Willing to relocate: Anywhere

Work Experience

Computer Lab Monitor

University of the Fraser Valley - Abbotsford, BC January 2022 to Present

Web Developer, IT Technician

Terranotics Tech Solutions Inc. - Abbotsford, BC September 2020 to Present

Working as an IT Technician, helping customers to set up their electronics, fixing/Installing Hardware, Designing Softwares & websites.

Produce Clerk (Part-time)

Chalo Freshco - Abbotsford, BC June 2021 to January 2022

Merchandiser

Shoppers Drug Mart / Pharmaprix - Abbotsford, BC March 2019 to September 2020

Working as an merchandiser, stocking up shelf, helping customers, doing planograms, low stocks, receiver , taking passport photographs and selling + recommending tech/electronics

Store Associate

Big Box Outlet Store - Abbotsford, BC May 2018 to November 2019

Working as a store associate, stocking up shelves, helping customers, doing planograms, low stocks, receiver, sales, cashier protocols.

Education

Bachelor's Degree in Computer science

University of the Fraser Valley - Abbotsford, BC Present

Skills

- JavaScript
- CSS
- PHP
- Java
- MySQL
- Git
- HTML5
- XML
- Linux
- C/C++
- User Interface (UI)

Languages

- English Expert
- Hindi Expert
- Punjabi Fluent
- Sanskrit Expert

Certifications and Licenses

Introductory digital marketing

March 2020 to Present

It was an online certification by google about digital marketing

Additional Information

SKILLS

- Reliable team worker
- Neat, clean and professional appearance
- Excellent multi-tasker
- punctual
- Customer service oriented
- Time management

SHUBHAM RISHI

1-2830, BOURQUIN CR.WEST ABBOTSFORD, BC, CANADA, V2S5N8